[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Translated in English, what does the name of the chinchilla mean?", "correct_answer": "Little Chincha", "incorrect_answers": ["Little Chilean", "Little Chile", "Of Chincha"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the favorite weapon of Harada Sanosuke, the 10th unit captain of the Shinsengumi?", "correct_answer": "Spear", "incorrect_answers": ["Kozuka Blade", "Sword", "Shuriken"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Such the weather will be if at dusk the sky is red.", "correct_answer": "Dry", "incorrect_answers": ["Rainy", "Snowy", "Hot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays American journalist Maddy Bowen, the main female character in the movie Blood Diamond?", "correct_answer": "Jennifer Connelly", "incorrect_answers": ["Julia Stiles", "Rose McEwen", "Jennifer Aniston"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Darth Vader dies in Star Wars: Episode VI - Return of the Jedi.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Most plant groups became extinct during the Permo-Triassic extinction event.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Elvis Presley, who was keen on Peanut Butter and Banana sandwiches, passed away in what year?", "correct_answer": "1977", "incorrect_answers": ["1979", "1976", "1978"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the song playing in the Background, when Chance first meets up with his informant Ruth Lanier?", "correct_answer": "Lullaby - Wang Chung", "incorrect_answers": ["Black/Red/Black - Wang Chung", "L.A. - Gil Scott Heron", "Every Other City - author unknown"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first  guest on The Tonight Show  when Johnny Carson was the host?", "correct_answer": "Groucho Marx", "incorrect_answers": ["Bette Midler", "Bob Hope", "Steve Allen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Orange and this color are the colors of  the holiday Halloween.", "correct_answer": "Black", "incorrect_answers": ["White", "Purple", "Red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following are old time cartoon characters?", "correct_answer": "Mutt and Jeff", "incorrect_answers": ["Fibber McGee and Molly", "Amos and Andy", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie was the following tag line used to promote: They figured he was a lazy time wasting slacker. They were right.", "correct_answer": "The Big Lebowski", "incorrect_answers": ["Deuce Bigalow : Male Gigalo", "True Romance", "Joe Dirt"]}]